<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Rapes In India: Breaking The Silence]]></title>
  <link href="http://savewomen.50bucks.info/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://savewomen.50bucks.info/"/>
  <updated>2015-06-15T07:50:56+10:00</updated>
  <id>http://savewomen.50bucks.info/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[A Human!]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2012 Delhi Gang Rape Case]]></title>
    <link href="http://savewomen.50bucks.info/blog/2012/12/22/2012-Delhi-gang-rape-case/"/>
    <updated>2012-12-22T18:37:24+11:00</updated>
    <id>http://savewomen.50bucks.info/blog/2012/12/22/2012-Delhi-gang-rape-case</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Join fight against Delhi gang-rape</p>

<p>Today 22nd Dec 2012, when I try to google on topic “Delhi News”, I am getting a page full with headlines updating status of the 23 yrs girls gang raped and who underwent the extremity of brutality anyone has ever imagined of, the misdeed or heinousness to a human being which no one could have ever thought of doing with even any animal. So the only question which comes to my mind is; will the google be displaying any update after a month?</p>

<p>The girl could have died and probably this incidence could never have been highlighted, and who knows that these kinds of incidences have never happened before. But everything happens, happens for a reason. God has given everyone an opportunity to think beyond his own life and how we, as human being, can maintain peace and happiness.</p>

<p>Everyone is shouting loud, asking death penalty, and doing everything to have justice immediately at this moment, but has anyone thought about the real problem? Has anyone think about what each and every person can do to avoid similar incidences in future?</p>

<p>I am a human being just like you and I don’t have any idea how to solve this problem. But I believe that we can find solution if we get united and I have decided to find a solution. Therefore I have booked a domain <a href="http://helpwomen.asia">http://helpwomen.asia</a> and will definitely take further steps.</p>

<p>At this particular time, I just expect a small favour from each of you. Before everyone goes busy again with his routine life and this horrific assault becomes a history,  I want to save feelings of everyone, the feeling which you have at the moment, the feeling which might fade away with time. Would you be able to spare out few words to express your feeling to the girl? If you have already expressed your feelings then please copy and paste it again or specify all relevant links to this page.</p>

<p>I am not sure if the girl will to able to win the battle of her life, but if she wins, then at least these  feelings will bring a smile on her face as this page will be added to the above wiki page. I think this will probably be the best thing you can do in the year 2012.</p>

<p>Wish everyone a good luck for the year 2013 and may GOD give the girl enough strength.</p>

<p>Thanks you.</p>

<p>A Human.</p>

<p>Here are some of the ways you can action :</p>

<blockquote><ol>
<li>Sign the online petition filed by Hindustand Times against Shiela Dixit.
<a href="http://www.change.org/en-IN/petitions/union-home-ministry-delhi-government-set-up-fast-track-courts-to-hear-rape-gangrape-cases">http://www.change.org/en-IN/petitions/union-home-ministry-delhi-government-set-up-fast-track-courts-to-hear-rape-gangrape-cases</a></li>
<li>Update Wiki page
<a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/2012_Delhi_gang_rape_case">http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/2012_Delhi_gang_rape_case</a></li>
<li>Donate for this cause
<a href="https://www.fundraise.com/drishti-direction/save-women-india-delhi-gang-rape">https://www.fundraise.com/drishti-direction/save-women-india-delhi-gang-rape</a></li>
<li>What should we ask to Government???
Ask government for creating a central online database to handle each and RAPE cases with the details on progress. Every citizen should have access to see the progress and right to protest if not satisfied. Let us fight collectively rather than let the victim and family fight for.</li>
</ol>
</blockquote>

<p>Let us improve our system.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
